Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part Two
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Autograph Items by Category, 1666-1961; Series I; 12.1; (32 boxes)
  - SCIENTISTS
    - Lambert, Aylmer Bourke, 1761-1842, undated (Box 26, Folder 1298)
    - Lamplugh, G.W. (George William), 1859- 1926, 1899 (Box 26, Folder 1299)
    - Lankester, E.R. (Edwin Ray), Sir, 1847-1929, 1897-1906, undated (Box 26, Folder 1300)
    - Lauder, Thomas Dick, Sir, 1784-1848, undated (Box 26, Folder 1301)
    - Lardner, Dionysus, 1793-1859, undated (Box 26, Folder 1302)
    - Lawrence, J.E., 1865 (Box 26, Folder 1303)
    - Lawson, M.A., 1875 (Box 26, Folder 1304)
    - Layard, Austen Henry, Sir, 1817-1894, 1853 (Box 26, Folder 1305)
    - Leake, William Martin, 1777-1860, undated (Box 26, Folder 1306)
    - Lee, Henry, 1826-1888, 1877 (Box 26, Folder 1307)
    - Lee, John, 1783-1866, 1824-29 (Box 26, Folder 1308)
    - Leighton, William Allport, 1805-1889, 1868, undated (Box 26, Folder 1309)
    - Leslie, John, Sir, 1766-1832, 1829 (Box 26, Folder 1310)
    - Lindley, John, 1799-1865, 1821 (Box 26, Folder 1311)
    - Liveing, George Downing, 1827-1924, undated (Box 26, Folder 1312)
    - Lockyer, Norman, Sir, 1836-1920, 1899 (Box 26, Folder 1313)
    - Lodge, Oliver, Sir, 1851-1940, 1934, undated (Box 26, Folder 1314)
    - Lott, Professor, 1855 (Box 26, Folder 1315)
    - Loudon, J.C. (John Claudius), 1783- 1843, 1817-21, undated (Box 26, Folder 1316)
    - Lowe, E.J., 1857 (Box 26, Folder 1317)
    - Lowe, Richard Thomas, 1802-1874, undated (Box 26, Folder 1318)
    - Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913, 1880-94, undated (Box 26, Folder 1319)
    - Lyell, Charles, Sir, 1797-1875, undated (Box 26, Folder 1320)
    - Macclesfield, George Parker, Earl of, 1697-1764, undated (Box 27, Folder 1321)
    - Mackie, Samuel Joseph, undated (Box 27, Folder 1322)
    - Maclaren, Charles, 1782-1866, undated (Box 27, Folder 1323)
    - Main, T. (Thomas), 1818-1885, 1852 (Box 27, Folder 1324)
    - Manby, George William, 1765-1854, 1826-45 (Box 27, Folder 1325)
    - Mansel-Pleydell, John Clavell, 1817- 1901, 1898, undated (Box 27, Folder 1326)
    - Martin, John, 1789-1869, 1849 (Box 27, Folder 1327)
    - McClelland, J., 1832 (Box 27, Folder 1328)
    - Meldola, Raphael, 1849-1915, 1898 (Box 27, Folder 1329)
    - Mill, Hugh Robert, 1861-1950, 1919 (Box 27, Folder 1330)
    - Miller, Hugh, 1802-1856, undated (Box 27, Folder 1331)
    - Miller, W.H. (William Hallowes), 1801- 1880, 1849 (Box 27, Folder 1332)
    - Miller, William Allen, 1817-1870, 1867 (Box 27, Folder 1333)
    - Mivart, St. George Jackson, 1827-1900, 1897 (Box 27, Folder 1334)
    - Molyneux, Samuel, 1689-1728, 1716 (Box 27, Folder 1335)
    - Morris, Daniel, Sir, 1844-1933, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 1336)
    - Morris, F.O. (Francis Orpen), 1810- 1893, 1870-90 (Box 27, Folder 1337)
    - Mosley, Oswald, Sir, 1785-1871, 1842 (Box 27, Folder 1338)
    - Mudge, Thomas, 1717-1794, undated (Box 27, Folder 1339)
    - Mueller, Ferdinand von, 1825-1896, undated (Box 27, Folder 1340)
    - Murchison, Roderick Impey, Sir, 1792- 1871, 1856-70, undated (Box 27, Folder 1341)
    - Murray, A.S. (Alexander Stuart), 1841- 1904, undated (Box 27, Folder 1342)
    - Museum d'histoire naturelle au Jardin du Roi, undated (Box 27, Folder 1343)
    - Nesbit, J.C. (John Collis), 1818-1862, 1856 (Box 27, Folder 1344)
    - Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907, 1877-82, undated (Box 27, Folder 1345)
    - Newton, Edwin Tulley, 1840-1930, 1896 (Box 27, Folder 1346)
    - Nopsca, Ferencz, baro, 1877-1933, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 1347)
    - Northumberland, Charlotte Florentie, Duchess of, d. 1866, undated (Box 27, Folder 1348)
    - O'Brien, M. (Matthew), 1814-1855, undated (Box 27, Folder 1349)
    - Odling, William, 1829-1921, undated (Box 27, Folder 1350)
    - Ogilvie, Francis G., Sir, 1858-1930, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 1351)
    - Ogilvie-Grant, William Robert, 1863- 1924, 1912 (Box 27, Folder 1352)
    - Oliver, Daniel, 1830-1916, 1863-84 (Box 27, Folder 1353)
    - Orlandos, Ioannes, d. 1852, 1825 (Box 27, Folder 1354)
    - Owen, Richard, 1804-1892, 1853-81 (Box 27, Folder 1355)
    - Paget, George Edward, Sir, 1809-1892, undated (Box 27, Folder 1356)
    - Paget, James, Sir, 1814-1899, 1869-78 (Box 27, Folder 1357)
    - Parkes, Samuel, 1759-1825, 1823 (Box 27, Folder 1358)
    - Peacock, George, 1791-1858, undated (Box 27, Folder 1359)
    - Pengelly, William, 1812-1894, 1862-91, undated (Box 27, Folder 1360)
    - Pepper, John Henry, 1821-1900, undated (Box 27, Folder 1361)
    - Pernet, George, 1861-1940, undated (Box 27, Folder 1362)
    - Phillips, John, 1800-1874, 1867, undated (Box 27, Folder 1363)
    - Phillips, William, 1775-1828, undated (Box 27, Folder 1364)
    - Pitt, Frances, 1888-1964, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 1365)
    - Pitt-Rivers, Augustus Henry Lane-Fox, 1827-1900, 1873 (Box 27, Folder 1366)
    - Playfair, Lyon Playfair, Baron, 1818- 1898, 1886-94, undated (Box 27, Folder 1367)
    - Pockels, A., 1820 (Box 27, Folder 1368)
    - Powell, R. Douglas (Richard Douglas), Sir, 1842-1925, 1891-97 (Box 27, Folder 1369)
    - Pratt, Anne, 1806-1893, 1858-74 (Box 27, Folder 1370)
    - Preston, S., 1785 (Box 27, Folder 1371)
    - Price, Bartholomew, 1818-1898, 1892 (Box 27, Folder 1372)
    - Price, M.P., 1904 (Box 27, Folder 1373)
    - Prince, C.L. (Charles Leeson), 1821- 1899 (Box 27, Folder 1374)
    - Proctor, Richard A. (Richard Anthony), 1837-1888, 1883 (Box 27, Folder 1375)
    - Ramsay, William, 1852-1916, undated (Box 27, Folder 1376)
    - Ranyard, Arthur Cowper, 1845-1894, 1880-93 (Box 27, Folder 1377)
    - Reade, Joseph Bancroft, 1801-1870, 1862 (Box 27, Folder 1378)
    - Redesdale, John Mitford, Baron, 1748- 1830, undated (Box 27, Folder 1379)
    - Redwood, T., undated (Box 27, Folder 1380)
    - Reeve, Lovell, 1814-1865, 1856 (Box 27, Folder 1381)
    - Richardson, Benjamin Ward, Sir, 1828- 1896, 1876 (Box 27, Folder 1382)
    - Rivers, George Pitt-Rivers, Baron, 1810-1866, undated (Box 27, Folder 1383)
    - Roberts-Austen, W.C. (William Chandler), Sir, 1843-1902, 1895 (Box 27, Folder 1384)
    - Roberts, William, Sir, 1830-1899, 1897 (Box 27, Folder 1385)
    - Robinson, Frederick Byron, 1893 (Box 27, Folder 1386)
    - Robinson, W. (William), 1838-1935, 1887-1916, undated (Box 27, Folder 1387)
    - Roemer, Karl Ferdinand, 1809-1869, undated (Box 27, Folder 1388)
    - Rogenhofer, Alois Friedrich, 1831-1897, 1872-77, undated (Box 27, Folder 1389)
    - Rolleston, George, 1829-1881, 1880 (Box 27, Folder 1390)
    - Rosse, William Parsons, Earl of, 1800- 1867, 1827, undated (Box 27, Folder 1391)
    - Rotheram, John, 1751-1804, undated (Box 27, Folder 1392)
    - Rucker, Arthur William, Sir, 1848-1915, 1898 (Box 27, Folder 1393)
    - Sabine, Edward, Sir, 1788-1883, 1850-63, undated (Box 28, Folder 1394)
    - Sabine, Joseph, 1770-1837, 1818 (Box 28, Folder 1395)
    - Salvin, Osbert, 1835-1898, 1883-89 (Box 28, Folder 1396)
    - Saunders, Edward, 1848-1910, 1904 (Box 28, Folder 1397)
    - Scharf, George, 1788-1860, 1834 (Box 28, Folder 1398)
    - Schomburgk, Moritz Richard, 1811-1891, 1886 (Box 28, Folder 1399)
    - Schroter, Rev., undated (Box 28, Folder 1400)
    - Sedgwick, Adam, 1785-1873, 1854, undated (Box 28, Folder 1401)
    - Seemann, Berthold, 1825-1871, 1852 (Box 28, Folder 1402)
    - Selby, Prideaux John, 1788-1867, 1823 (Box 28, Folder 1403)
    - Seward, A.C. (Albert Charles), 1863- 1941, 1913 (Box 28, Folder 1404)
    - Sharpe, Richard Bowdler, 1847-1909, 1876-90 (Box 28, Folder 1405)
    - Smith, Edgar A., 1887 (Box 28, Folder 1406)
    - Smyth, C. Piazzi (Charles Piazzi), 1819-1900, undated (Box 28, Folder 1407)
    - South, James, 1785-1867, undated (Box 28, Folder 1408)
    - South, Richard, d. 1932, 1891 (Box 28, Folder 1409)
    - Sowerby, George Brettingham, 1788-1854, 1844 (Box 28, Folder 1410)
    - Sowerby, James de Carle, 1787-1871, 1819 (Box 28, Folder 1411)
    - Smith, J., 1880 (Box 28, Folder 1412)
    - Spilsburg, Bernard H., Sir, 1878-1947, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 1413)
    - Spottiswoode, William, 1825-1883, 1875-83 (Box 28, Folder 1414)
    - Stainton, H.T. (Henry Tibbats), 1822- 1892, 1864 (Box 28, Folder 1415)
    - Stocks, J.E., 1822-1854, undated (Box 28, Folder 1416)
    - Stokes, George Gabriel, Sir, 1819-1903, 1901 (Box 28, Folder 1417)
    - Stone, William, 1857-1958, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 1418)
    - Story-Maskelyne, Nevil, 1823-1911, 1867 (Box 28, Folder 1419)
    - Sylvester, James Joseph, 1814-1897, 1888, undated (Box 28, Folder 1420)
    - Syme, James, 1799-1870, undated (Box 28, Folder 1421)
    - Taylor, Brook, 1685-1731, undated (Box 28, Folder 1422)
    - Teall, J.J.H. (Jethro Justinian Harms), 1849-1924, 1899-1906 (Box 28, Folder 1423)
    - Tennant, James, 1808-1881, 1872 (Box 28, Folder 1424)
    - Thirkill, H., b. 1886, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 1425)
    - Thistleton-Dyer, William T. (William Turner), 1843-1928, 1896-1907 (Box 28, Folder 1426)
    - Thomas, J.J. (Joseph John), Sir, 1856- 1940, 1919 (Box 28, Folder 1427)
    - Thompson, Silvanus Phillips, 1851-1916, undated (Box 28, Folder 1428)
    - Tipping, H. Avray (Henry Avray), 1855- 1933, 1910-31 (Box 28, Folder 1429)
    - Trevelyan, Walter Calverley, Sir, 1797-1879, 1855, undated (Box 28, Folder 1430)
    - Trevor-Battye, Aubyn Bernard Rochefort, 1835-1922, 1895-1917 (Box 28, Folder 1431)
    - Tristram, H.B. (Henry Baker), 1822- 1906, undated (Box 28, Folder 1432)
    - Tylor, Edward Burnett, Sir, 1832-1917, undated (Box 28, Folder 1433)
    - Tyndall, John, 1820-1893, 1899-1902, undated (Box 28, Folder 1434)
    - Unidentified, 1806 (Box 28, Folder 1435)
    - Ure, Andrew, 1778-1857, undated (Box 28, Folder 1436)
    - Vines, Sydney, Howard, 1849-1934, 1895, undated (Box 28, Folder 1437)
    - Wallace, Alfred Russell, 1823-1913, 1911-13 (Box 28, Folder 1438)
    - Walsingham, Thomas de Grey, Baron, 1843-1919, 1880-89 (Box 28, Folder 1439)
    - Ward, Francis Kingdon, 1885-1958, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 1440)
    - Waterhouse, Charles Owen, 1843-1917, 1883-85 (Box 28, Folder 1441)
    - Watson, Hewett Cottrell, 1804-1881, 1859 (Box 28, Folder 1442)
    - Watson, W., undated (Box 28, Folder 1443)
    - Watts, W.W. (William Whitehead), b. 1860, 1907-08 (Box 28, Folder 1444)
    - Webster, Charles, 1844 (Box 28, Folder 1445)
    - Welsh, William, 1859-1925, 1900 (Box 28, Folder 1446)
    - Westwood, J.O. (John Obadiah), 1805- 1893, 1866 (Box 28, Folder 1447)
    - Wheatstone, Charles, Sir, 1802-1875, 1855 (Box 28, Folder 1448)
    - Whewell, William, 1794-1866, 1828-54, undated (Box 28, Folder 1449)
    - White, Gilbert, 1720-1793, undated (Box 28, Folder 1450)
    - Wight, Robert, 1796-1872, undated (Box 28, Folder 1451)
    - Wilkinson, Gardner, 1861 (Box 28, Folder 1452)
    - Williamson, Henry, 1897-1977, 1927, undated (Box 28, Folder 1453)
    - Wilson, Erasmus, Sir, 1809-1884, 1868, undated (Box 28, Folder 1454)
    - Wollaston, William Hyde, 1766-1828, 1827 (Box 28, Folder 1455)
    - Wolseley, Frances Garnet Wolseley, Viscountess, 1872-1936, 1895-1919, undated (Box 28, Folder 1456)
    - Wood, J.G. (John George), 1827-1889, undated (Box 28, Folder 1457)
    - Woodward, Arthur Smith, 1864-1944, 1897-1906 (Box 28, Folder 1458)
    - Woodward, Henry, 1832-1921, 1909 (Box 28, Folder 1459)
    - Woodward, Horace B. (Horace Bolingbroke), 1848-1914, 1906 (Box 28, Folder 1460)
    - Woodward, Samuel Peckworth, 1821-1865, 1860 (Box 28, Folder 1461)
    - Wright, Dudley, 1868-1949, 1910 (Box 28, Folder 1462)
    - Yarrell, William, 1784-1856, 1832-55 (Box 28, Folder 1463)
    - Yelloly, John, 1774-1842, 1837 (Box 28, Folder 1464)
  - TEMPERANCE MOVEMENT
    - Balfour, Clara Lucas, 1878 (Box 29, Folder 1465)
    - Burns, Jabez, 1854 (Box 29, Folder 1466)
    - Busch, August, 1932 (Box 29, Folder 1467)
    - Caine, William Sproston, 1842-1903, 1890, undated (Box 29, Folder 1468)
    - Carlisle, George James Howard, Earl of, 1843-1911, 1892-1901 (Box 29, Folder 1469)
    - Collins, Stephen, Sir, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 1470)
    - Comstock, Anthony, 1844-1915, 1888 (Box 29, Folder 1471)
    - Denman, Baron, 1805-1894, 1882 (Box 29, Folder 1472)
    - Gough, John Ballantine, 1817-1886, 1854-81 (Box 29, Folder 1473)
    - Hawkins, John H., 1799-1858, 1849 (Box 29, Folder 1474)
    - Horsley, Victor Alexander, 1857-1916, undated (Box 29, Folder 1475)
    - Hunt, G. W., 1861 (Box 29, Folder 1476)
    - Lawson, Wilfrid, Sir, 1829-1906, 1861-1904 (Box 29, Folder 1477)
    - Leahy, Patrick, Abp. of Cashel, 1806-1875, undated (Box 29, Folder 1478)
    - Mathew, Theobald, 1790-1856, 1845, undated (Box 29, Folder 1479)
    - McKee, John, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 1480)
    - Meyer, Frederick Brotherton, 1847-1929, 1916-29 (Box 29, Folder 1481)
    - Murphy, Francis, undated (Box 29, Folder 1482)
    - Nöel-Buxton, Nöel Edward, Baron, 1869-1948, 1927, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 1483)
    - O'Neil, J., of Halifax, 1816 (Box 29, Folder 1484)
    - Pope, Samuel, 1826-1901, 1869 (Box 29, Folder 1485)
    - Richardson, Benjamin Ward, Sir, 1828-1896, 1882 (Box 29, Folder 1486)
    - Robinson, S., undated (Box 29, Folder 1487)
    - Scott, Henry M., 1911 (Box 29, Folder 1488)
    - Sherlock, Frederick, 1853-1914, 1884 (Box 29, Folder 1489)
    - Somerset, Isabel, Lady, 1851-1921, 1909-11 (Box 29, Folder 1490)
    - Strafford, George Stevens Byng, Earl of, 1806-1886, 1877 (Box 29, Folder 1491)
    - Volstead, A. J. (Andrew John), 1860-1947, 1922, 1928 (Box 29, Folder 1492)
    - Warren, Charles, Sir, 1840-1927, 1887 (Box 29, Folder 1493)
    - Walton, A. O., undated (Box 29, Folder 1494)
    - Watson, Claude A., undated (Box 29, Folder 1495)
    - Whittaker, Thomas Palmer, Sir, 1850-1919, 1914 (Box 29, Folder 1496)
    - Williams, Frances Elizabeth, 1839-1898, 1894 (Box 29, Folder 1497)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 29, Folder 1498)
  - THEATER
    - Alexander, George, Sir, 1858-1918, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 1499)
    - Anderson, James R. (James Robertson), 1811-1895, undated (Box 30, Folder 1500)
    - Anderson, Mary, 1859-1940, 1878 (Box 30, Folder 1501)
    - Archer, Thomas, 1789?-1848, undated (Box 30, Folder 1502)
    - Arliss, George, 1868-1946, undated (Box 30, Folder 1503)
    - Arnold, Charles, 1899 (Box 30, Folder 1504)
    - Arthur, Julia, undated (Box 30, Folder 1505)
    - Bancroft, Marie, 1839-1921, undated (Box 30, Folder 1506)
    - Bancroft, Squire, 1841-1926, 1903-1912 (Box 30, Folder 1507)
    - Barrett, Wilson, 1848-1904, 1885 (Box 30, Folder 1508)
    - Barrie, J.M. (James Matthew), 1860- 1937, undated (Box 30, Folder 1509)
    - Bateman, Kate Josephine, 1842-1917, undated (Box 30, Folder 1510)
    - Becher, Elizabeth, Lady, 1791-1872, 1862 (Box 30, Folder 1511)
    - Beere, Bernard, Mrs., 1856-1915, undated (Box 30, Folder 1512)
    - Belford, F.W., undated (Box 30, Folder 1513)
    - Bellew, Harold Kyle, 1855-1911, undated (Box 30, Folder 1514)
    - Beringer, Oscar, Mrs., 1856-1936, 1902 (Box 30, Folder 1515)
    - Beverly, Henry Roxby, 1796-1863, undated (Box 30, Folder 1516)
    - Blanche, Ada, undated (Box 30, Folder 1517)
    - Bland, W.H., undated (Box 30, Folder 1518)
    - Blunt, Arthur Cecil, 1844-1896, 1886 (Box 30, Folder 1519)
    - Borgherst, A., undated (Box 30, Folder 1520)
    - Boucicault, Dion, 1820-1890, undated (Box 30, Folder 1521)
    - Braithwaite, Lilian, d. 1948, undated (Box 30, Folder 1522)
    - Brandram, Samuel, 1824-1892, 1883-1891 (Box 30, Folder 1523)
    - Branscombe, Maud, undated (Box 30, Folder 1524)
    - Brookfield, Charles H.E. (Charles Hallam Elton), 1857-1913, 1890 (Box 30, Folder 1525)
    - Brough, Lionel, 1836-1909, undated (Box 30, Folder 1526)
    - Brough, William, 1826-1870, 1864-1865 (Box 30, Folder 1527)
    - Browne-Potter, Cora, Mrs., 1859-1936, undated (Box 30, Folder 1528)
    - Brydone, Alfred, 1900 (Box 30, Folder 1529)
    - Buchel, Charles A., undated (Box 30, Folder 1530)
    - Buckstone, Fred, undated (Box 30, Folder 1531)
    - Buckstone, John Baldwin, 1802-1879, 1851-1867 (Box 30, Folder 1532)
    - Bufton, Eleanor, 1840-1893, undated (Box 30, Folder 1533)
    - Bunn, Alfred, 1796-1860, undated (Box 30, Folder 1534)
    - Burnand, F.C. (Francis Cowley), Sir, 1836-1917, 1899 (Box 30, Folder 1535)
    - Byron, Henry J. (Henry James), 1835- 1884, 1875 (Box 30, Folder 1536)
    - Calmour, Alfred C. (Alfred Cecil), 1857?-1912, 1901 (Box 30, Folder 1537)
    - Campbell, Patrick, Mrs., 1865-1940, undated (Box 30, Folder 1538)
    - Capper, Alfred, d. 1921, 1885-1920 (Box 30, Folder 1539)
    - Caradoci-Allan, Maria Caterina Rosalbine, 1800-1865, undated (Box 30, Folder 1540)
    - Carlisle, Sybil, Miss, undated (Box 30, Folder 1541)
    - Carr, J. Comyns (Joseph Comyns), 1849-1916, 1881-1897 (Box 30, Folder 1542)
    - Carroll, George, undated (Box 30, Folder 1543)
    - Carter, Leslie, d. 1908, undated (Box 30, Folder 1544)
    - Carton, R.C. (Richard Claude), 1856- 1928, 1897-1899 (Box 30, Folder 1545)
    - Cartwright, Charles, b. 1855, undated (Box 30, Folder 1546)
    - Castillan, A., 1853 (Box 30, Folder 1547)
    - Cautley, Laurence, 1893 (Box 30, Folder 1548)
    - Cavendish, Ada, 1839-1895, 1872 (Box 30, Folder 1549)
    - Chambers, C. Haddon (Charles Haddon), 1860-1921, undated (Box 30, Folder 1550)
    - Charing Cross Theatre, undated (Box 30, Folder 1551)
    - Chart, N. Nye, Mrs., 1880 (Box 30, Folder 1552)
    - Chatterley, Louisa, undated (Box 30, Folder 1553)
    - Chevalier, Albert, 1861-1923, undated (Box 30, Folder 1554)
    - Chaway (?), Robert, undated (Box 30, Folder 1555)
    - Chorley, Henry Fothergill, 1808-1872, undated (Box 30, Folder 1556)
    - Clayton, John, 1843-1888, undated (Box 30, Folder 1557)
    - Coffin, C. Hayden, 1862-1935, undated (Box 30, Folder 1558)
    - Coghlan, Rose, 1853-1932, 1903 (Box 30, Folder 1559)
    - Collette, Charles, 1842-1924, 1879-1897 (Box 30, Folder 1560)
    - Collins, Arthur P., 1863-1932, undated (Box 30, Folder 1561)
    - Collins, Frank, b. 1878, undated (Box 30, Folder 1562)
    - Cooke, T.P. (Thomas Potter), 1786- 1864, undated (Box 30, Folder 1563)
    - Cooper-Cliffe, W.H., 1900 (Box 30, Folder 1564)
    - Corelli, Marie, 1855-1929, undated (Box 30, Folder 1565)
    - Coyne, Joseph, b. 1867, undated (Box 30, Folder 1566)
    - Coyne, J. Stirling (Joseph Stirling), 1803-1868, undated (Box 30, Folder 1567)
    - Craven, H.T., 1864 (Box 30, Folder 1568)
    - Crystal Palace, 1883 (Box 30, Folder 1569)
    - Daly, Arnold, undated (Box 31, Folder 1570)
    - Daly, Thomas Augustine, 1838-1899, undated (Box 31, Folder 1571)
    - Dare, Phyllis, b. 1890, undated (Box 31, Folder 1572)
    - Darnley, Evelyn, undated (Box 31, Folder 1573)
    - Davenport, Fanny, undated (Box 31, Folder 1574)
    - Day(?), Phillip, undated (Box 31, Folder 1575)
    - De Frece's Minstrels, undated (Box 31, Folder 1576)
    - D'Oyly Carte, Richard, 1844-1901, 1897 (Box 31, Folder 1577)
    - Earle, Charles, undated (Box 31, Folder 1578)
    - Edwardes, George, 1852-1915, 1899 (Box 31, Folder 1579)
    - Edwards, Conway, 1870 (Box 31, Folder 1580)
    - Edwards, H. Sutherland (Henry Sutherland), 1828-1906, 1876-1894 (Box 31, Folder 1581)
    - Edwards, John Spencer, d. 1916, 1900 (Box 31, Folder 1582)
    - Eldred, John, undated (Box 31, Folder 1583)
    - Elliston, R.W. (Robert Williams), 1774-1831, undated (Box 31, Folder 1584)
    - Emden, W.S. (William Samuel), 1801?- 1872, 1871? (Box 31, Folder 1585)
    - Emery, Pollie, undated (Box 31, Folder 1586)
    - Emery, Winifred, 1902? (Box 31, Folder 1587)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, 1909-2000, undated (Box 31, Folder 1588)
    - Farnie, H.B. (Henry Bougham), 1836- 1889, 1879 (Box 31, Folder 1589)
    - Farnie, Pearl, Mrs., 1861 (Box 31, Folder 1590)
    - Farquhar, Gilbert, 1850-1920, 1899 (Box 31, Folder 1591)
    - Faucit, Helen Saville, 1817-1898, undated (Box 31, Folder 1592)
    - Faversham, William, 1868-1940, undated (Box 31, Folder 1593)
    - Fawcett, A.J., 1869 (Box 31, Folder 1594)
    - Fealy, Maude, undated (Box 31, Folder 1595)
    - Fechter, Charles, 1924-1879, 1864 (Box 31, Folder 1596)
    - Fernald, Chester Bailey, 1869-1938, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 1597)
    - Forbes-Robertson, Johnston, Sir, 1853- 1937, 1893-1910 (Box 31, Folder 1598)
    - Fredericks, William S., 1836 (Box 31, Folder 1599)
    - Garvice, Charles, d. 1920, undated (Box 31, Folder 1600)
    - Giddens, George, 1855-1920, 1891 (Box 31, Folder 1601)
    - Glaser, Lulu, 1903 (Box 31, Folder 1602)
    - Gonza, Algar, d. 1882, undated (Box 31, Folder 1603)
    - Goodwin, Nat. C. (Nathaniel Carll) 1857-1919, undated (Box 31, Folder 1604)
    - Grain, Corney, 1844-1895, 1890 (Box 31, Folder 1605)
    - Green, John, 1801-1874, 1856 (Box 31, Folder 1606)
    - Greene, Evie, undated (Box 31, Folder 1607)
    - Grey, Katherine, undated (Box 31, Folder 1608)
    - Grimaldi, Joseph, 1779-1837, 1823 (Box 31, Folder 1609)
    - Grossmith, Weedon, 1852-1919, undated (Box 31, Folder 1610)
    - Hardy, Nelson, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 1611)
    - Hare, John, Sir, undated (Box 31, Folder 1612)
    - Harned, Virginia, 1868-1946, 1892 (Box 31, Folder 1613)
    - Harris, A. (Augustus), 1825-1873, 1869-73 (Box 31, Folder 1614)
    - Harrison, Clifford, 1900? (Box 31, Folder 1615)
    - Haworth, Joseph, undated (Box 31, Folder 1616)
    - Haymarket Theatre, Programme, 1882 (Box 31, Folder 1617)
    - Heath (?), Lionel, undated (Box 31, Folder 1618)
    - Herne, Chrystal, 1904 (Box 31, Folder 1619)
    - Holt, Maud, 1863-1937, undated (Box 31, Folder 1620)
    - Hopper, De Wolf, 1858-1935, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 1621)
    - Howard, Bronson, 1842-1908, 1907 (Box 31, Folder 1622)
    - Irving, Henry, Sir, 1838-1905, 1888 (Box 32, Folder 1623)
    - Ivy House, Programme, 1890 (Box 32, Folder 1624)
    - Jannuschek, Madam, undated (Box 32, Folder 1625)
    - Jeffreys, Ellis, b. 1868, 1900 (Box 32, Folder 1626)
    - Jones, W.G., Mrs., 1874 (Box 32, Folder 1627)
    - Kalich, Bertha, undated (Box 32, Folder 1628)
    - Kean, Charles John, 1811?-1868, 1851 (Box 32, Folder 1629)
    - Kemble, Fanny, 1809-1893, undated (Box 32, Folder 1630)
    - Kendal, Madge, 1849-1935, undated (Box 32, Folder 1631)
    - Kendal, William Hunter, 1843-1917, undated (Box 32, Folder 1632)
    - Liston, John, 1776?-1846, 1840 (Box 32, Folder 1633)
    - Lyric Theatre, Playbill, undated (Box 32, Folder 1634)
    - MacCabe, Frederick, 1892 (Box 32, Folder 1635)
    - Madison Square Theatre, Programme, undated (Box 32, Folder 1636)
    - Manbury, Lily, undated (Box 32, Folder 1637)
    - Marlowe, Julia, 1865-1950, 1901 (Box 32, Folder 1638)
    - Marston, Westland, 1819-1890, 1876 (Box 32, Folder 1639)
    - Martin-Harvey, John, Sir, 1863-1944, undated (Box 32, Folder 1640)
    - Matthews, Marie, 1865 (Box 32, Folder 1641)
    - Mills, Frank, 1899 (Box 32, Folder 1642)
    - Milton, Ernest, 1892-, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 1643)
    - Modjeska, Helena, 1840-1909, 1882 (Box 32, Folder 1644)
    - Pepper, John Henry, 1821-1900, 1865 (Box 32, Folder 1645)
    - Peterly Manor, amateur theatre troupe, 1877 (Box 32, Folder 1646)
    - Philpotts, Eden, undated (Box 32, Folder 1647)
    - Planche, James Robinson, 1796-1880, 1840s (Box 32, Folder 1648)
    - Potter, Cora Urquhart, 1859-1936, undated (Box 32, Folder 1649)
    - Princess' Theatre, 1860 (Box 32, Folder 1650)
    - Pyne, Louisa, 1828-1904, undated (Box 32, Folder 1651)
    - Rehan, Ada, 1860-1916, 1891 (Box 32, Folder 1652)
    - Rich, John, 1682?-1761, 1719 (Box 32, Folder 1653)
    - Robson, Frederick, 1822?-1864, undated (Box 32, Folder 1654)
    - Rousby, William Wybert, 1835-1907, 1869 (Box 32, Folder 1655)
    - Royal Surrey Theatre, Admittance note, 1850s (Box 32, Folder 1656)
    - Saker, Annie, b. 1870, undated (Box 32, Folder 1657)
    - Salvini, Tommaso, 1829-1916, 1883 (Box 32, Folder 1658)
    - Sarong, G., 1880s (Box 32, Folder 1659)